http://www.huntonly.com/privacy-policy.html

HuntOnly Inc. Privacy Policy
HuntOnly Inc. is a general audience web site, and does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under 13 years of age.
COLLECTION: COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION BY HUNTONLY INC. General. HUNTONLY INC. collects personally identifiable information (that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address or telephone number) only in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect Personally Identifiable Information from you, it is because you voluntarily submit the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, chats or bulletin boards, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information.
HUNTONLY INC. website may be linked to websites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a HUNTONLY INC. logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by HUNTONLY INC.. HUNTONLY INC. website may also carry advertisements from other companies. HUNTONLY INC. is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you've left a HUNTONLY INC. site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any Personally Identifiable Information they collect from you.
Some of the advertisements that appear on HUNTONLY INC. website are delivered to you by national Internet advertising and application companies. These companies ultilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to our site(s), including information about the banner ads they display, any cookie they place on your computer and your IP address.
CHOICE: HUNTONLY INC. Will Provide You with Choices About the Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information
HUNTONLY INC. will not use the you information provide to us for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted or share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties that are not affiliated with HUNTONLY INC., unless we obtain your permission.
USE: HUNTONLY INC.'s Use of PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION HUNTONLY INC. will use your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION provided under this Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If HUNTONLY INC. obtains PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy.
HUNTONLY INC. employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION.
HUNTONLY INC. may share your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses) but they may only use your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to provide HUNTONLY INC. with a specific service and not for any other purpose.
HUNTONLY INC. may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows HUNTONLY INC. to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on our web sites. Your non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION and click stream data about your activities on our sites may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purposes. Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with HUNTONLY INC.'s advertisers and business partners.
There may be instances when HUNTONLY INC. may disclose PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of HUNTONLY INC.; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if HUNTONLY INC. sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, HUNTONLY INC. may transfer your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to a third party as part of that transaction.
SECURITY: HUNTONLY INC. Protects the Security of PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
HUNTONLY INC. uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, HUNTONLY INC. uses reasonable methods to make sure that PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.
Southern Maryland Waterfowl Season - 2014/2015
play
Tweets by @HuntOnly
Awesome Moose Video Footage
play
August Goose Hunting in ND
Early season goose hunting opportunities for North Dakota Sportsmen. North Dakota Game and Fish Biologist Doug Leier reports on the history and importance of the August Goose Season.
View more...
